[{"answer": "It just would. He was always the same", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Don't know", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Since when did he drink whisky", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nobody seems to know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Is he", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend. my friend Paice", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What you doing around here then", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, I didn't know that", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm straight.  Respectable", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, you've been watching television", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I work for him", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Yes, I do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That, my friend? That's another hundred", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Three hundred altogether, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "While he was here. You went about together", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Was he", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Was he", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yeah, I'll do you a favour", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How'd it happen, then", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Was he", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Who paid you to see me off", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes you can", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, don't my friend, don't", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "That little shit", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What about my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You wouldn't", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " 'Cos I know you wear purple underwear", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I might have guessed", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And what orders would they be, Con", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What does he want that bloody great country place for", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What kind of entertaining", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Not entirely. No", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Sure I'm sure", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Now tell me the truth", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "And you didn't know her last name", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Last Sunday afternoon, my friend and two of his boys arrive with my friend and tell me that he's rumbled. Somehow, he's seen the film and was about to shoot his mouth off. They ask me for some whisky and start forcing it down his throat.  I thought they'd just duff him up a bit. Honest", "docId": "Get-Carter.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Nothing. What could I do", "qsentId": 38}]